Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - War/ Watch Foundation (Box 295)
  - Washburn University (Box 295)
  - Washington DOC: Straight Talk About Health, Seattle, WA (Box 295)
  - Washington (DC) Free Press (Box 295)
  - Washington (DC) Institute of Mental Hygiene (Box 295)
  - The Washington Post (Box 295)
  - The Washington Spectator (Box 295)
  - Washington University, St Louis, MO (Box 295)
  - Wausau (Wisconsin) Area P.T.A. Council (Box 295)
  - Way, Mrs. (Box 295)
  - Wayfarer Marine, Camden, ME (Box 295)
  - WBAI New York, NY (Box 295)
  - WBTV, Charlotte, NC (Box 295)
  - WBZ-TV, Boston, MA (Box 296)
  - WCIX TV Miami, FL (Box 296)
  - WDIV TV4 Detroit, MI (Box 296)
  - WEEI Radio, Boston, MA (Box 296)
  - Weekend Magazine, Ottawa, ON (Box 296)
  - Weil, Gunther (Box 296)
  - Weinberger, Caspar W. (Box 296)
  - Weiss, Peter and Cora (Box 296)
  - Weiss, Ted (Box 296)
  - Weitzman, Lenore J. (Box 296)
  - The Welfare Federation, Cleveland, OH (Box 296)
  - Welner, Renee (Box 296)
  - Wentworth, Carter (Box 296)
  - Werner, Kedren (Box 296)
  - Wessel, Morris A. (Box 296)
  - West Suburban Intercollegiate Council, Chicago, IL (Box 296)
  - West Virginia University (Box 296)
  - Westchester Academy of Medicine: Dental Section, Scarsdale, NY (Box 296)
  - Wester, Jesse M. (Box 296)
  - Western Institute for Group and Family Therapy, Watsonville, CA (Box 296)
  - Western Kentucky University (Box 296)
  - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinics, Pittsburgh, PA (Box 296)
  - Western Reserve University, 1955-1958; 7 folders (Box 297)
  - Western Reserve University, 1959-1961; 6 folders (Box 298)
  - Western Reserve University, 1962-1963; 6 folders (Box 299)
  - Western Reserve University, 1964-1966; 6 folders (Box 300)
  - Western Reserve University, 1966-1972; 4 folders (Box 301)
  - Westinghouse Broadcasting (Box 301)
  - WEWS-TV, Cleveland, OH (Box 301)
  - Wheatley, George M. (Box 301)
  - White, Charles W. (Box 301)
  - White, E. B. (Box 301)
  - White, Joel and Allene (Box 301)
  - White Americans to Support Black Liberation (Box 301)
  - The White House Conference on Children and Youth (Box 301)
  - The White House Conference on Families (Box 301)
  - The White House Conference on International Cooperation (Box 301)
  - Whitehead, Fred (Box 301)
  - Whitney, Thomas P. (Box 302)
  - Whitney Communications Corporation (Box 302)
  - Who's Who in American Politics (Box 302)
  - WICE Radio, Providence, RI (Box 302)
  - Wicker, Tom (Box 302)
  - Wilbert Productions (Box 302)
  - Wilder, F. Fessenden (Box 302)
  - Wilkerson, Cathy (Box 302)
  - Wilkinson, Charles Burnham ("Bud"), See President's Council on Youth Fitness.
  - Willey, Robert (Box 302)
  - William Morrow and Company (Box 302)
  - Williams, Benjamin H. (Box 302)
  - Williams, Harrison A., Jr. (Box 302)
  - Williams, Hosea (Box 302)
  - Williams, Patti (Box 302)
  - Williams, Roger Neville (Box 302)
  - Willis, Judith A. (Box 302)
  - Wilson, Alfred M. (Box 302)
  - Wilson, Dagmar Searchinger (Box 302)
  - WIN (Box 302)
  - Wingerhoff, Nettie (Box 302)
  - Winnicott, D.W. (Box 302)
  - Winter, Ella (Box 302)
  - Winters, Shelley (Box 302)
  - Wisconsin Public Radio (Box 302)
  - Wisdom (Box 302)
  - WJBK-TV, Detroit, MI (Box 302)
  - WKYC, Cleveland, OH (Box 302)
  - WLCY Radio, St Petersburg, FL (Box 302)
  - WLS-TV Chicago, IL (Box 302)
  - WMEX, New York, NY (Box 302)
  - WNAC-TV, Boston, MA (Box 302)
  - WNBC-TV, New York, NY (Box 302)
  - WNET/13, New York, NY (Box 302)
  - WNEW-TV New York, NY (Box 302)
  - WNHC, New Haven, CT (Box 302)
  - WNWS-South Florida (Box 302)
  - WOC Broadcasting Company, Davenport, IA (Box 302)
  - Wolper Productions, Inc. (Box 302)
  - Woman [magazine] (Box 302)
  - Woman's Day (Box 302)
  - Woman's Home Companion (Box 303)
  - Women For: (Box 303)
  - Women for a Meaningful Summit (Box 303)
  - Women for Peace (Box 303)
  - Women Strike for Peace, 2 folders (Box 303)
  - Women U.S.A., See Abzug, Bella.
  - Women's Action for Nuclear Disarmament (Box 303)
  - Women's American ORT (Box 303)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 303)
  - Women's International Liaison Committee for International Cooperation Year (Box 303)
  - Women's Macrobiotic Society Newsletter (Box 303)
  - Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (Box 303)
  - Women's Peace Education Project, New York, NY (Box 303)
  - Woodbury, Marda (Box 303)
  - Woolfolk, William (Box 303)
  - The Wooster Clinic, Wooster, OH (Box 303)
  - WOR-TV, New York, NY (Box 303)
  - World Affairs Information Center, Westport, CT (Box 303)
  - World Assembly for Peace (Box 303)
  - World Book Publishing (Box 304)
  - World Citizen, Inc. (Box 304)
  - World Committee for a World Constitutional Convention, Inc. (Box 304)
  - World Conference on Religion and race (Box 304)
  - World Conference on Vietnam, Stockholm, 2 folders (Box 304)
  - World Constitutional Convention (Box 304)
  - World Federalist Association (Box 304)
  - World Federation for Mental Health (Box 304)
  - World Health Day (Box 304)
  - World Law Fund (Box 304)
  - World Organization for Human Potential (Box 304)
  - World Peace Council (Box 304)
  - World Peacemakers (Box 304)
  - World Poetry Conference, Stony Brook, NY (Box 304)
  - The World Publishing Company (Box 304)
  - World Unity Through the Arts (Box 304)
  - World Without War Publications (Box 304)
  - WPTR, Albany, NY (Box 304)
  - WQXR, New York, NY (Box 304)
  - Wright, Gary, See Family correspondence.
  - Wright, Virginia, and Ralph, See Family correspondence.
  - Writers and Editors War Tax Project (Box 304)
  - WTNH-TV, New Haven, CT (Box 304)
  - WTOP-TV, Washington, DC (Box 304)
  - WTVN-Radio, Columbus, OH (Box 304)
  - WUSA Kingsport, TN (Box 304)
  - W. W. Norton & Company, Inc. (Box 304)
  - WXYZ Radio, Southfield, MI (Box 304)
  - Wyckoff, Hogie (Box 305)
  - Wyden, Peter H. (Box 305)
  - WYES, New Orleans, LA (Box 305)
  - Yaffa Syndicate Pty., Ltd. Australia (Box 305)
  - The Yale Crew Association (Box 305)
  - Yale Medical School Alumni Fund (Box 305)
  - Yale Political Union (Box 305)
  - Yale University (Box 305)
  - Yale University (Box 306)
  - Yale University Alumni (Box 306)
  - Yale University Child Study Center (Box 306)
  - Yale University Press (Box 306)
  - Yamamoto, Shizuko (Box 306)
  - Yankee [magazine] (Box 306)
  - Yankee Books (Box 306)
  - Yarborough, Ralph (Box 306)
  - Yates, Sidney R. (Box 306)
  - Yes On A Committee, Santa Cruz, CA (Box 306)
  - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny (Box 306)
  - Yoakum, Robert H. (Box 306)
  - The York (ON) Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 306)
  - Yoshindo Kobunsha, Tokyo (Box 306)
  - Young, Andrew (Box 306)
  - Young, Foster H., Jr. (Box 306)
  - Young, Louise (Box 306)
  - Young, Milton R. (Box 306)
  - Young, Mort (Box 306)
  - Young, Stephen M. (Box 306)
  - Young, Whitney M., Jr. (Box 306)
  - Young Presidents' Oganization, Inc. (Box 306)
  - Young & Rubicam, Inc. (Box 306)
  - Young Workers Liberation League (Box 306)
  - Youth [magazine] (Box 306)
  - Youth Against War and Fascism (Box 306)
  - Youth International Party (Box 306)
  - Zablocki, Clement B. (Box 306)
  - Zachry, Nancy (Box 306)
  - Zero Population Growth (Box 306)
  - Zerosei (Box 307)
  - Zeta Psi Fraternity (Box 307)
  - Ziferstein, Isidore (Box 307)
  - Zimmerman, Mitchell (Box 307)
  - Zucker, Barry (Box 307)
  - Zutran, Eric (Box 307)
  - Zweig, Connie (Box 307)
- DrSpock.com
  Following Dr. Spock's death, his widow Mary Morgan continued his legacy through formation of a company and associated website, drspock.com. This series contains material relating to the formation, operation, and eventual sale of the company; development of website content, policies, and structure; and correspondence with companies regarding potential joint projects.
  - [General correspondence], Sep 1996-Apr 2000; 14 folders (Box 308)
  - [General correspondence], Jun 2000-Nov 2000; 9 folders (Box 309)
  - [General correspondence], Dec 2000-Mar 2001; 8 folders (Box 310)
  - [General correspondence], 2001, Mar-Jul; 8 folders (Box 311)
  - [General correspondence], Aug 2001-2004; 9 folders (Box 312)
  - [General correspondence], 2006-2008 (Box 313)
  - [General correspondence], undated; 2 folders (Box 313)
  - Abbot Labs (Box 313)
  - ABC (Box 313)
  - Adam.com, 2 folders (Box 313)
  - ADHD Toolkit (Box 313)
  - Advance Publications (Box 313)
  - AMC Beauty (Box 313)
  - American Baby Basket (Box 313)
  - American Red Cross (Box 313)
  - American Red Cross, 3 folders (Box 314)
  - AOL, 5 folders (Box 314)
  - AOL (Box 315)
  - AOL (Box 315)
  - Apple Computer (Box 315)
  - Article programs, "program" here refers to topics or subject areas for articles (Box 315)
  - Articles, A-Cl, original articles written for the drspock.com website; 5 folders (Box 315)
  - Articles, Co-G, original articles written for the drspock.com website; 8 folders (Box 316)
  - Articles, H-O, original articles written for the drspock.com website; 8 folders (Box 317)
  - Articles, P-S, original articles written for the drspock.com website; 9 folders (Box 318)
  - Articles, T-Y, original articles written for the drspock.com website; 9 folders (Box 319)
  - Authors, potential, resumes, samples, etc. (Box 320)
  - Awards (Box 320)
  - Baby Basics (Box 320)
  - Baby Center Inc. (Box 320)
  - Baby Talk (Box 320)
  - Balmex (Box 320)
  - Barton Schmitt MD (Box 320)
  - BDInteractive (Greg Bender) (Box 320)
  - Bertelsmann (Box 320)
  - Board of Directors, 2000, Mar-Jun; 3 folders (Box 320)
  - Board of Directors, 2000, Jul-Dec; 3 folders (Box 321)
  - Board of Directors, 2001; 2 folders (Box 321)
  - Board of Directors, 2003 (Box 321)
  - Board of Directors, undated (Box 321)
  - Brand building plan, general (Box 321)
  - Brand building plan, Shandwick (Box 322)
  - Brand building plan, 3 Ring Circus (Box 322)
  - Brand building plan, Tipping Sprung (Box 321)
  - Brand building plan, Tipping Sprung (Box 322)
  - Bringing Up Baby (BBC film) (Box 322)
  - Business plans, 4 folders (Box 322)
  - Certificate of incorporation, Delaware (Box 322)
  - "Chat" functionality (Box 322)
  - Cheerios (Box 322)
  - Child Health Corporation of America (CHCA) (Box 322)
  - Children's Care Portal (Box 323)
  - Cleveland Clinic, proposals for several projects, including parenting library; "Clinic Expert" negotiations; 4 folders (Box 323)
  - Cleveland Clinic (Box 323)
  - Company overview (Box 323)
  - Competitor comparisons, 2 folders (Box 323)
  - Consultant agreements, Kim Heilman, Bjorn Foster, Media Encounters/Larry Grossman, Melissa Tervet (Box 323)
  - Contact lists, board of directors, employee, organizational, personal (Box 323)
  - Cosmetic Essence (Box 324)
  - Corporate bonus plan (Box 324)
  - Disclaimer (Box 324)
  - Discovery, Inc., 2 folders (Box 324)
  - Distribution strategy (Box 324)
  - Domain names and registration, 3 folders (Box 324)
  - Dr. Spock magazine (Box 325)
  - drkoop.com (Box 325)
  - Employee manual (Box 325)
  - Employment agreements (Box 325)
  - Ethics, sample policies, discussions, notes, etc. (Box 325)
  - Experts, lists of, purpose of, etc. (Box 325)
  - Family-friendly car features (Box 325)
  - FAQs, questions and responses, some with discussion; 2 folders (Box 325)
  - FAQs, questions and responses, some with discussion; 3 folders (Box 326)
  - Financial, 2 folders (Box 326)
  - Food Fit (Box 326)
  - Ford "Boost America" campaign (Box 326)
  - Ford "Boost America" campaign, 5 folders (Box 327)
  - Functional requirements (Box 327)
  - Glossary (Box 327)
  - GNC (Box 327)
  - Hachette (Box 327)
  - "Healthy Start" series (Box 328)
  - Hearst (Box 328)
  - Holidays content, articles, toy reviews, etc.; 2 folders (Box 328)
  - Intellectual property, trademark research, licensing discussions, what Spock material the company owned and did not own, etc.; 2 folders (Box 328)
  - Jebsen Agency / Joana Jebsen, 2 folders (Box 328)
  - Johnson & Johnson (Box 329)
  - JP Morgan (Box 329)
  - Kimberly-Clark (Huggies) (Box 329)
  - Leapfrog survey, brand strategy and vision; 2 folders (Box 329)
  - Letterhead and business cards (Box 329)
  - LLC paperwork, Maine (Box 329)
  - Logo research, 2 folders (Box 329)
  - Lucille Packard Children's Hospital (LPCH) (Box 329)
  - Macrobiotics, includes essay by Spock (Box 329)
  - Mailing / organization lists (Box 329)
  - Malpractice issues (Box 329)
  - March of Dimes (Box 329)
  - Martha Stewart, 2 folders (Box 329)
  - Mary Morgan agreements, licensing agreements, employment agreement, resume, etc. (Box 330)
  - "Media Coverage" binder, press coverage of the website; originally in 3-ring binder, pages removed and foldered (Box 330)
    See also Press coverage; Press kit.
  - Medical-ethical advisory board (Box 330)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, Shelton and Buckley (Box 330)
  - Merchandising, various possibilities (Box 330)
  - Meredith Corp. (Box 330)
  - Merger agreements (Box 330)
  - MSN (Box 330)
  - Name awareness and marketing study (Box 330)
  - Name awareness and marketing study, 5 folders (Box 331)
  - Newsletters, printouts of various other sites' newsletters, with commentary (Box 331)
  - Nondisclosure agreements (Box 331)
  - Notes, miscellaneous, sketches, notes, flowcharts, etc. on large sheets of flip-chart paper; site layout, roles and responsibilities, etc. (Oversize 6)
  - "Parent Sense" series (Box 331)
  - "Parent Sense" series, includes scripts; 2 folders (Box 332)
  - Parenting channel proposal (Box 332)
  - Parenting library (Box 332)
    See also Cleveland Clinic.
  - Parenting magazine (Box 332)
  - Parenting program series (BBC, PBS) (Box 332)
  - Partnership possibilities (Box 332)
  - "Pathways of Learning" quiz, 4 folders (Box 332)
  - Penguin Dutton (Baby Magic) (Box 333)
  - Pharmaceutical partnerships, lists of possibilities (Box 333)
  - Policies, editorial, security, ethics, vacation, travel, etc.; 2 folders (Box 333)
  - Preliminary research (Box 333)
  - Press coverage, 2 folders (Box 333)
    See also "Media Coverage" binder.
  - Press coverage (Box 334)
  - Press kit (Box 334)
  - Press releases (Box 334)
  - PRIMEDIA (Box 334)
  - Privacy, research, discussions, sample policies, etc.; 2 folders (Box 334)
  - Product possibilities (Box 334)
  - Program development process, "program" here refers to topics or subject areas for articles (Box 334)
  - QualKids (Box 334)
  - Reader's Digest (Box 334)
  - Restricted stock purchase agreement (Box 334)
  - Revenue sources (Box 335)
  - Rodale, 2 folders (Box 335)
  - Royalties, from various Spock titles (Box 335)
  - Safety / first aid book, 3 folders (Box 335)
  - Sale, possible buyers, corporate information packet, etc.; 2 folders (Box 335)
  - Sample contracts and agreements (Box 335)
  - Scholastic (Box 335)
  - Scholastic, 2 folders (Box 336)
  - Sheppard, Mullin, Richter and Hampton, 2 folders (Box 336)
  - Sickle cell articles, 3 folders (Box 336)
  - Sickle cell videos (NCMHD) (Box 336)
  - Specifications, for website content (Box 336)
  - Spock bios for website (Box 336)
  - Sponsorship policy/ecommerce policy (Box 337)
  - Stay At Home Readiness Kit (Box 337)
  - Stein, Marty, editor of two Spock collections for Pocket Books; see also Writings: Dr. Spock: The First Two Years and Writings: Dr. Spock: The School Years (Box 337)
  - Story ideas (Box 337)
  - Street Law, 2 folders (Box 337)
  - Style guide (Box 337)
  - Sweetchild Software (Box 337)
  - "Take Charge" parenting guides (Box 337)
  - Teens (Box 337)
  - Television and video, miscellaneous tv and video projects and ideas; 2 folders (Box 337)
  - Terminations (Box 337)
  - The Time Factory (Box 338)
  - Tools, quizzes, charts, checklists etc. for posting to website (Box 338)
  - Tribune syndicated agreement (Box 338)
  - TV series focus group (Box 338)
  - ViaCom (Box 338)
  - Walt Disney, 3 folders (Box 338)
  - WebMD (Box 339)
  - Website "about" page, drafts of text, discussions, etc. (Box 339)
  - "Website crew and authors" (Box 339)
  - Website hosting (Box 339)
  - Website images (Box 339)
  - Website structure, diagrams, discussion, etc. (Box 339)
  - Website traffic, reports, analysis, etc. (Box 339)
- Legal material
  - Contracts
    - Apple Computer, Inc., 1999 (Box 340)
    - Blue Plate Productions, Inc., 1988-1998; 2 folders (Box 340)
    - CEL Communications, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 340)
    - Child Care Productions, 1985 (Box 340)
    - The Childhood Project, Inc., 1991 (Box 340)
    - Curtis Publishing Company, 1951-1963 (Box 340)
    - Dan-Dee International, Ltd., 2006 (Box 340)
    - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, 1953-1958 (Box 340)
    - HBO, 1986 (Box 340)
    - Hearst Corporation, 1984-1991 (Box 340)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1961-1986 (Box 340)
    - International Merchandising Corporation, 1998 (Box 341)
    - The Jebsen Agency, 1999 (Box 341)
    - Kurashi-no Techo Sha, Ltd., 1966 (Box 341)
    - M.C.E.G. Productions, Inc, 1988 (Box 341)
    - Macmillan Company, 1967 (Box 341)
    - Magni Group, Inc., 1996 (Box 341)
    - McCall Corporation, 1952-1971 (Box 341)
    - Meredith Press, 1962-1971 (Box 341)
    - Morgan, Mary, 1987 (Box 341)
    - National Broadcasting Company (NBC), 1955-1987 (Box 341)
    - Needleman, Robert, 2002 (Box 341)
    - Pantheon Books, 1989 (Box 341)
    - Parenting, 1991-1992 (Box 341)
    - Parker, Steven, 1994-2000 (Box 341)
    - Penguin Books USA, 1997 (Box 341)
    - Pocket Books, 1943-2003 (Box 341)
    - Ralph Jester Productions, 1951 (Box 341)
    - Random House, 1981 (Box 341)
    - Redbook Publishing Company, 1975-1991 (Box 341)
    - Rothenberg, Michael B., 1982-1990; co-author of two editions of Baby and Child Care; 3 folders (Box 342)
    - Simon & Schuster, Inc., 1959-2000; 2 folders (Box 342)
    - Time Warner Entertainment Company, L. P., 1996-1997 (Box 342)
    - VidAmerica - The Video Cassette Rental Club, Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 342)
    - Walt Disney Pictures, 1990-1993 (Box 342)
    - ZMC Productions, 1998 (Box 342)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 342)
  - Copyright
    - [General] (Box 342)
  - Divorce
    - Benjamin and Jane Spock, 1976 (Box 343)
    - Clifford and Mary Councille, 1975; 2 folders (Box 343)
  - Estates
    - Benjamin Spock:
      - 000 Correspondence, notes, research, Andrew Cook Claim (Box 344)
      - 001 Estate plan, 6 folders (Box 345)
      - 001 Estate plan, 6 folders (Box 346)
      - 001 Estate plan, 9 folders (Box 347)
      - 002 Mary Morgan estate (Box 347)
      - 003 Business and copyright matters, 2 folders (Box 348)
      - 003 Business and copyright matters, royalty statements, 6 folders (Box 349)
      - 003 Business and copyright matters, 11 folders (Box 350)
      - 003 Business and copyright matters, 6 folders (Box 351)
      - 004 Baby and Child Care, 6 folders (Box 352)
      - 005 Trademark, 6 folders (Box 353)
      - 006 Probate and tax, 12 folders (Box 354)
      - 007 Licensing, 2 folders (Box 355)
      - 007 Licensing, 6 folders (Box 356)
      - 007 Licensing, 3 folders (Box 357)
      - 008 Court papers, 9 folders (Box 358)
      - 009 Dr Spock website, 3 folders (Box 359)
        See also drspock.com.
      - Inter vivos trusts (Box 360)
      - Personal rights (Box 360)
      - Disarmament fund (Box 360)
      - Agreement between Benjamin Spock and Jane Spock (Box 360)
      - Agreement and renunciation (Box 360)
      - Correspondence (Box 360)
      - Werbin memorandum (Box 360)
      - Trust declaration (Box 360)
      - Working papers (Box 360)
      - Notes (Box 360)
      - Life insurance, Baby and Child Care rights (Box 361)
      - Trusts, 2 folders (Box 361)
      - Trusts, 5 folders (Box 362)
      - Trusts, 11 folders (Box 363)
      - Trusts (Box 364)
    - Mildred Spock (Box 364)
    - Robert Spock (Box 364)
    - Legal residence (Box 364)
  - Liquidation
    - Benjamin Spock Company, LLC (Box 364)
  - Litigation
    See also Correspondence-subject files: United States of America v. Coffin, Ferber, Goodman, Raskin and Spock 50 U.S.C. App. 462(a).
    - Benjamin M. Spock v District of Columbia Appeals No. 5860, 1971 (Box 364)
    - Councille et al. v Arkansas Activities Association LR-C-80-522, 1980 (Box 364)
    - Goodtime Home Video Corp v. Blue Plate Productions and Benjamin Spock, 1989; 2 folders (Box 364)
    - Morgan, Mary et al. v Marion S. Barry et al. Civil Action 81-1419, 1981 (Box 365)
    - Miriam Abramovitz et al. v James Aher et al. Civil Action N-77-207, 1977 (Box 365)
    - Spock v Commissioner of Internal Revenue, 1969 (Box 365)
    - Spock v David DC Civil Action No. 1621-72, 1972 (Box 365)
    - Spock v Grundig, 1981 (Box 365)
    - Spock v N.S.A 76Civ. 4457, 1976; 2 folders (Box 365)
    - Spock v Pocket Books, Inc., 1965 (Box 365)
    - Spock v Simon and Schuster, Inc 73Civ. 4958, 1973; 2 folders (Box 365)
    - United States v Hostetter, et al. DC Code 22-3102, 1973 (Box 366)
    - United States of America v Coffin, Ferber, Goodman, Raskin and Spock 50U.S.C. App. 462(a), 1968-1978; 20 printed official court documents; 2 folders (Box 366)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 366)
  - Mortgages
    - Carapace (boat) (Box 366)
  - Real estate
    - Camden, ME, 2 folders (Box 367)
    - Housing exchange (Box 367)
    - Menlo Park, CA (Box 367)
    - New York, NY (Box 367)
    - Pittsburgh, PA (Box 367)
    - Rogers, AR, 2 folders (Box 367)
    - San Diego, CA (Box 367)
    - Tortola, BVI (Box 367)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Visa applications (Box 367)
    - Voter registration (Box 367)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 367)
- Medical reference files
  These files were accumulated by Dr. Spock over the course of his life as a practicing pediatrian, child health advocate, and author. The topics are retained as listed on the original folders.
  - Abused child (Box 368)
  - Accidents (Box 368)
  - Adolescence (Box 368)
  - Adoption (Box 368)
  - Aggression (Box 368)
  - Air crib (Box 368)
  - Air pollution (Box 368)
  - Allergy (Box 368)
  - Anemia (Box 369)
  - Anthropology (Box 369)
  - Anthropometry (Box 369)
  - Anus (Box 369)
  - Arithmetic (Box 369)
  - Arteriosclerosis (Box 369)
  - Asthmatic children (Box 369)
  - Athletics (Box 369)
  - Atomic explosion injuries (Box 369)
  - Autism (Box 369)
  - Birth control (Box 369)
  - Blindness (Box 369)
  - Bone age (Box 369)
  - Books for children (Box 369)
  - Brain injury (Box 369)
  - Breast feeding (Box 369)
  - Bronchiolitis (Box 369)
  - Celiac disease (Box 369)
  - Cell biology (Box 369)
  - Cerebral palsy (Box 369)
  - Child Analysis (Box 370)
  - Child care practices (Box 370)
  - Child development (Box 370)
  - Child health (Box 370)
  - Child labor laws (Box 370)
  - Child psychiatry (Box 370)
  - Child psychiatry in the U.S.S.R. (Box 370)
  - Child psychosis (Box 370)
  - Child welfare (Box 370)
  - Children and the Cold War (Box 370)
  - Children's books (Box 370)
  - Cholecystitis and cholelithiasis (Box 370)
  - Cleft palate (Box 370)
  - Colic (Box 370)
  - College counselling (Box 370)
  - Communicable disease (Box 370)
  - Congenital defect (Box 370)
  - Constipation (Box 370)
  - Contraception (Box 370)
  - Crib Death (Box 370)
  - Crib Vibrator (Box 370)
  - Croup (Box 370)
  - Day Care (Box 370)
  - Deafness (Box 370)
  - Delinquency (Box 371)
  - Depression (Box 371)
  - Development (Box 371)
  - Diabetes (Box 371)
  - Diaper rash (Box 371)
  - Diaper service (Box 371)
  - Diarrhea (Box 371)
  - Diets (Box 371)
  - Drug addiction (Box 371)
  - Eczema (Box 371)
  - Educations (Box 372)
  - Ego (Box 372)
  - Elelctroencephalography (Box 372)
  - Embryology (Box 372)
  - Emergencies (Box 372)
  - Emotional Development (Box 372)
  - Endocrinology (Box 372)
  - Eneuresis, circumcision and masturbation (Box 372)
  - Enzyme systems (Box 372)
  - Epilepsy (Box 372)
  - Eye (Box 372)
  - Fallout shelters (Box 372)
  - Family health (Box 372)
  - Family life (Box 372)
  - Family size (Box 372)
  - Fathers (Box 372)